[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Macy"]}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNP", "POS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Where were you and what did you hear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I was inside Macy's at the Lancolme counter which is close to the entrance of the mall area where the shooter was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "I mean, do most people who work in shopping malls now in America have some kind of training for this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RBS", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "No, they don't have training for shootings.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "What is your view about this ongoing debate in America which I'm vociferous about, many people don't want it all about gun control and about the ability of people like the shooter to get their hands on a weapon of this power and magnitude?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Well, I feel like that, you know, there is not enough consequences in the United States and, you know, unfortunately, it starts from the home and the home is destructing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hawaii"]}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "What can you tell us about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "I -- I mean, I saw the post that he was moving to Hawaii.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Have you any idea where he may have stolen the gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "That -- I'm not aware of any of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Did he ever have any flare ups, any behavioral issues at all that would have suggested to you he could even be capable of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Did he have any family issues that you were aware of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Not that I'm aware of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "It's completely baffling to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "It absolutely is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Is the whole community just in deep shock about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Yes, you know, all of our friends just are trying to comprehend what he may have gone through or what could have happened that led him to do such a drastic thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Of his affiliation to guns at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "LESHIRE: I mean, I have seen it on his Facebook.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "What is your response to that particular argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "My response to that would be that would not be a good idea to have everyone in that theater or even a few people in that theater with a gun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "I suppose my obvious question to you, Allan Gottlieb, is this, is why would anybody in America who is not in the military or the police force need to ever have one of these weapons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "WRB", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Well, first of all, these aren't fully automatic weapons like you get in the military and many police departments have.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Allan Gottlieb"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Well, James Holmes shot 17 people, didn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "It only shoots one round --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James Holmes"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Can you stop talking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "If you want to get a good solution you've got to look at both sides of the equation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Hey, can you stop talking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "If you want to have a debate, you've got to look at both sides.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "-- that they should be allowed to continue to easily purchase or steal these weapons?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "I don't think -- Piers, I don't think deranged people should be able to have a gun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Why are you laughing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Because you're not telling the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Who do you encourage to be armed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "OTTLIEB: You should have the right to be -- you should have the right to be armed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2004"]}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "CD", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Doesn't that give you any alarm bell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I'll tell you what -- I'll tell you what makes alarm bells to me is that until 2004, following the ban on these assault weapons, then there was a ban on these AR-15s and now there isn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Do you have any idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 381, "question": "How many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "But to be honest with you --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Well, why don't you look at both sides?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "I'm going to give you both sides.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "You do the same math that I'm doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Yes, OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Do you feel comfortable that that is easy to do in your country, Mr. Gottlieb?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "It should be easy for law-abiding people, for people who are mentally -- mentally deranged or people who commit violent crimes know it shouldn't be and we need to work on that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Gottlieb"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Explain to me why anyone in America should have one of these?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "It is about this or a bomb or any weapon.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Are they evil children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Of course not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Then what do you do about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "People choke on hot dogs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "That's why -- the question is why should anyone -- anyone have an assault weapon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "MD", "VB", ":", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "They exist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Do you believe -- does the Second Amendment allow you to have a tank?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I think actually it does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Are you comfortable with everybody having a tank?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I think that that is not the debate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Is it something genuinely to be worried about, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "I think it is always something to be worried about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "What is your reaction to this extraordinary proliferation in gun sales?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Well, it's surprising.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "What is the answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Well, I personally believe that people have a right to protect themselves in their home, that they should be allowed to have a gun to protect them and their family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Do you think we'll ever see human beings on the Moon again, in your lifetime, in my lifetime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Well, you initially said ever, and ever is a long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Would you like to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Well, I would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "It's a nice children's book Why did you decide to do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "On my first space flight, we carried 18 mice on board for an experiment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "How's she doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "She's doing very well, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]